(Sheldon:)Don't worry, I didn't really say that.
(Sheldon:)I find the concept of coitus ridiculous
and off-putting.
(Amy:)Should have taken my breasts out
while I had the chance.
Mrs. Davis. Mrs. Davis. Mrs. Davis.
(Sheldon:)I know you're in there.
I saw your car in the parking lot.
(Janine:)What?
(Sheldon:)I just found out
that you recommended myself...
(Sheldon:)...Dr. Hofstadter and Dr. Koothrappali
to be on the short list for tenure.
(Janine:)Well, despite your quirks...
(Janine:)...the three of you are very accomplished
in your respective fields.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what you mean by quirks,
but I do want to express my gratitude.
- You didn't bring another gift, did you?
- No, no, I learned my lesson.
(Sheldon:)- I understand that was inappropriate.
- Good.
- Anyway, thank you.
- You're welcome.
(Janine:)I'm gonna pretend that didn't happen.
(Sheldon:)Right on, sister.